{"data":{"site":{"pathPrefix":null},"postgres":{"establishment":[{"establishmentid":"3751","name":"Manhattan Fish and Chicken","address":"3800 Conner","zipcode":"48215","owner":"Fadi Chaav","licenseNumber":"066459","licenseType":"Fixed Establishment","establishmentType":"Food Service Establishment","establishmentStatus":"Open","riskCategory":"Medium","reviewFrequencyDays":"180.0","coords":"-82.96729,42.38404","geojson":{"id":"3751","type":"Feature","geometry":{"type":"Point","coordinates":[-82.967285449,42.384039806]},"properties":{"name":"Manhattan Fish and Chicken","owner":"Fadi Chaav","address":"3800 Conner","zipcode":"48215","license_type":"Fixed Establishment","risk_category":"Medium","license_number":"066459","establishmentid":"3751","establishment_type":"Food Service Establishment","establishment_status":"Open","review_frequency_days":"180.0","most_recent_license_date":"5/7/2018"}},"nearbyList":[{"establishmentid":"680","name":"Burger King ","address":"12661 Mack Ave","zipcode":"48215"},{"establishmentid":"2646","name":"McDonald's #25135","address":"3975 Conner Ave","zipcode":"48215"},{"establishmentid":"1731","name":"Capuchin Kitchen","address":"4390 Conner ","zipcode":"48215"},{"establishmentid":"1104","name":"Maison Fine Food Inc.","address":"13031 Mack Ave","zipcode":"48215"},{"establishmentid":"2766","name":"Wendy's ","address":"4749 Conner St","zipcode":"48215"},{"establishmentid":"3893","name":"Northeast Guidance Center","address":"2900 Conner","zipcode":"48215"},{"establishmentid":"5425","name":"Spud Headz","address":"12700 E Warren","zipcode":"48215"},{"establishmentid":"5240","name":"Red Sea Food Inc.","address":"12500 E Warren","zipcode":"48215"},{"establishmentid":"51622565","name":"Tasty Bob's","address":"13000 E Warren Ave","zipcode":"48215"},{"establishmentid":"5191","name":"UAW Local 7","address":"2600 Conner Ave","zipcode":"48215"}],"inspectionsByEstablishmentidList":[{"inspectionid":"44304","inspectionDate":"2018-11-27T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"2-301.12","violationDescription":"FOOD EMPLOYEES shall properly wash their hands and exposed portions of their arms for at least 20 seconds and thoroughly rinsing with clean water. EMPLOYEES shall pay particular attention to the areas underneath the fingernails and between the fingers. (P)","violationType":"Priority","itemDescription":"Employee(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Used common towel","subProblem":"Hanging from apron/uniform","location":"ESTABLISHMENT","subLocation":"At the Handsink","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2018-12-06T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Remove and discontinue use."},{"violationCode":"4-302.12","violationDescription":"(A) FOOD TEMPERATURE MEASURING DEVICES shall be provided and readily accessible for use in ensuring attainment and maintenance of FOOD temperatures as specified under Chapter 3. (Pf)   \r\n(B) A TEMPERATURE MEASURING DEVICE with a suitable small-diameter probe that is designed to measure the temperature of thin masses shall be provided and readily accessible to accurately measure the temperature in thin FOODS such as MEAT patties and FISH filets. (Pf)\r\n","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":"Food thermometer(s)","subItem":"probe","problemDescription":"Not available","subProblem":"","location":"ESTABLISHMENT","subLocation":"Missing Digital Thermometer","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2018-12-06T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Make available at all times."},{"violationCode":"6-301.12","violationDescription":"Each HANDWASHING SINK or group of adjacent HANDWASHING SINKS shall be provided with:\r\n(A) Individual, disposable towels; (Pf)\r\n(B) A continuous towel system that supplies the user with a clean towel;(Pf) or \r\n(C) A heated-air hand drying device.(Pf)\r\n(D) A hand drying device that employs an air-knife system that delivers high velocity pressurized air at ambient temperatures.(Pf)\r\n","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":"Sanitary hand drying provisions","subItem":"disposable, paper towels","problemDescription":"Not provided","subProblem":"At hand sink","location":"ESTABLISHMENT","subLocation":"Missing Paper toweling","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2018-12-06T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Provide"},{"violationCode":"4-204.112","violationDescription":"(A)  In a mechanically refrigerated or hot FOOD storage unit, the sensor of a TEMPERATURE MEASURING DEVICE shall be located to measure the air temperature in the warmest part of a mechanically refrigerated unit and in the coolest part of a hot FOOD storage unit.\r\n(B)  Cold or hot holding EQUIPMENT used for POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS FOOD shall be designed to include and shall be equipped with at least one integral or permanently affixed TEMPERATURE MEASURING DEVICE that is located to allow easy viewing of the device's temperature display (EXCEPT, heat lamps, cold plates, steam tables, or other equipment where it is not practical).\r\n(C)  TEMPERATURE MEASURING DEVICES shall be designed to be easily readable.\r\n(D)  FOOD TEMPERATURE MEASURING DEVICES and water TEMPERATURE MEASURING DEVICES on WAREWASHING machines shall have a numerical scale, printed record, or digital readout in increments no greater than 1C or 2F in the intended range of use. (Pf)\r\n\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Thermometer(s)","subItem":"refrigeration","problemDescription":"Not provided","subProblem":"","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"Missing Thermometer(s)","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2018-12-06T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Provide."},{"violationCode":"4-501.11","violationDescription":"EQUIPMENT shall be maintained in a state of repair and condition that meets the requirements of the code.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Equipment","subItem":"","problemDescription":"In poor repair","subProblem":"","location":"ESTABLISHMENT","subLocation":"Inside the Cooler (2 door)","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":"2018-12-06T00:00:00","correctionDescription":null},{"violationCode":"6-101.11","violationDescription":"Materials for indoor floor, wall, and ceiling surfaces under conditions of normal use shall be:\r\n(1) SMOOTH, durable, and EASILY CLEANABLE for areas where FOOD ESTABLISHMENT operations are conducted;\r\n(2) Closely woven and EASILY CLEANABLE carpet for carpeted areas; and\r\n(3) Nonabsorbent for areas subject to moisture such as FOOD preparation areas, walk-in refrigerators, WAREWASHING areas, toilet rooms, mobile FOOD ESTABLISHMENT SERVICING AREAS, and areas subject to flushing or spray cleaning methods.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Floor(s)","subItem":"floor covering(s)","problemDescription":"Not constructed, designed, installed to be","subProblem":"Easily cleanable","location":"ESTABLISHMENT","subLocation":"In front of the Cooking equipment","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":"2018-12-06T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Repair/replace to be smooth and easily cleanable."}]},{"inspectionid":"40893","inspectionDate":"2017-11-21T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"6-301.12","violationDescription":"Each HANDWASHING SINK or group of adjacent HANDWASHING SINKS shall be provided with:\r\n(A) Individual, disposable towels; (Pf)\r\n(B) A continuous towel system that supplies the user with a clean towel;(Pf) or \r\n(C) A heated-air hand drying device.(Pf)\r\n(D) A hand drying device that employs an air-knife system that delivers high velocity pressurized air at ambient temperatures.(Pf)\r\n","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":"Sanitary hand drying provisions","subItem":"disposable, paper towels","problemDescription":"Not provided","subProblem":"At hand sink","location":"ESTABLISHMENT","subLocation":"Missing Paper toweling","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2017-12-07T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Provide"},{"violationCode":"6-201.13","violationDescription":"(A) In FOOD ESTABLISHMENTS in which cleaning methods other than water flushing are used for cleaning floors, the floor and wall junctures shall be coved and closed to no larger than one thirty-second inch.\r\n(B) The floors in FOOD ESTABLISHMENTS in which water flush cleaning methods are used shall be provided with drains and be graded to drain, and the floor and wall junctures shall be coved and SEALED.","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Floor(s)","subItem":"juncture","problemDescription":"Not coved","subProblem":"","location":"RESTROOM (UNISEX)","subLocation":"Missing Coved molding","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":"2017-12-07T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Provide / install coved molding."}]},{"inspectionid":"37042","inspectionDate":"2016-11-08T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"No","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"7-204.11","violationDescription":"Chemical SANITIZERS and other chemical antimicrobials applied to FOOD-CONTACT SURFACES shall meet the requirements specified in this code. (P)\r\n","violationType":"Priority","itemDescription":"Sanitizer(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Do not comply with law","subProblem":"","location":"RESTAURANT","subLocation":"At the Sanitizer","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2016-11-22T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Provide labels that comply with law."},{"violationCode":"4-302.14","violationDescription":"A test kit or other device that accurately measures the concentration in mg/L of SANITIZING solutions shall be provided. (Pf)\r\n","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":"Sanitizer test kit","subItem":"chlorine","problemDescription":"Not provided","subProblem":"","location":"RESTAURANT","subLocation":"At the Test strips","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2016-11-22T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Provide as required"},{"violationCode":"6-301.12","violationDescription":"Each HANDWASHING SINK or group of adjacent HANDWASHING SINKS shall be provided with:\r\n(A) Individual, disposable towels; (Pf)\r\n(B) A continuous towel system that supplies the user with a clean towel;(Pf) or \r\n(C) A heated-air hand drying device.(Pf)\r\n(D) A hand drying device that employs an air-knife system that delivers high velocity pressurized air at ambient temperatures.(Pf)\r\n","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":"Sanitary hand drying provisions","subItem":"disposable, paper towels","problemDescription":"Not provided","subProblem":"At hand sink","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"At the Handsink","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2016-11-22T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Provide"},{"violationCode":"5-205.11","violationDescription":"(A) A HANDWASHING SINK shall be maintained so that it is accessible at all times for EMPLOYEE use and used for no other purpose. (Pf)\r\n(B)  An automatic handwashing facility shall be used in accordance with manufacturer's instructions. (Pf)\r\n","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":"Handwashing sink(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not easily accessible","subProblem":"Items stored In","location":"DISHWASHING AREA","subLocation":"At the Handsink","corrected":"No","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Remove items from handsink.  Do not store items at handsink."},{"violationCode":"4-501.11","violationDescription":"EQUIPMENT shall be maintained in a state of repair and condition that meets the requirements of the code.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Equipment components","subItem":"seals","problemDescription":"Broken","subProblem":"","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"At the Cooler (3  door)","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":"2016-11-22T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Repair/replace."},{"violationCode":"5-205.15","violationDescription":"A PLUMBING SYSTEM shall be:\r\n(A) Repaired according to LAW; (P) and\r\n(B) Maintained in good repair.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Plumbing system","subItem":"water line(s)","problemDescription":"Not maintained","subProblem":"","location":"DISHWASHING AREA","subLocation":"At the Sink(s)","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Maintain in good repair"},{"violationCode":"4-602.13","violationDescription":"NonFOOD-CONTACT SURFACES of EQUIPMENT shall be cleaned at a frequency necessary to preclude accumulation of soil residues.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Nonfood contact surface(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Soiled","subProblem":"","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"At the Freezer (upright)","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Keep clean."},{"violationCode":"5-205.15","violationDescription":"A PLUMBING SYSTEM shall be:\r\n(A) Repaired according to LAW; (P) and\r\n(B) Maintained in good repair.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Plumbing system","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not maintained","subProblem":"","location":"RESTROOM (EMPLOYEE)","subLocation":"At the Toilet","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Maintain in good repair"},{"violationCode":"6-501.12","violationDescription":"(A) PHYSICAL FACILITIES shall be cleaned as often as necessary to keep them clean.\r\n(B) Except spill cleanup, cleaning shall be done during periods when the least amount of FOOD is exposed such as after closing. ","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Physical facilities/structures","subItem":"ceiling","problemDescription":"Soiled","subProblem":"","location":"RESTAURANT","subLocation":"At the Casing / cover around fan","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":"2016-11-22T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Keep clean."},{"violationCode":"6-201.15","violationDescription":"Mats and duckboards shall be designed to be removable and EASILY CLEANABLE.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Mat(s)/duckboard(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not easily cleanable","subProblem":"","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"At the Floor","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":"2016-11-08T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Repair/replace to be easily cleanable."}]}]}]}},"pageContext":{"eid":"3751"}}